in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can take your initials or any
你怎么才能把你名字的首字母或任何
series of letters and use them to create
一系列字母，并使用它们来创建
a logo where the letters overlap each
字母相互重叠的徽标
other and to follow along with what I'm
其他和跟随我的是什么
doing here in this tutorial I'm going to
在本教程中，我将介绍
recommend that you download and install
建议您下载并安装
this font that I used for this logo
我用来做这个徽标的字体
design because this font works really
设计，因为这个字体真的很好用
well for this sort of thing so check the
嗯，对于这类事情，请检查
description of the video for a download
下载视频的描述
link to that font and install it before
链接到该字体并在此之前安装
you launch inkscape and then you'll be
你推出Inkscape，然后你就会
good to go so let's get rid of this and
好了，走吧，让我们把这个处理掉
we'll get started here I'm going to grab
我们从这里开始，我要抓起
my my text tool and I'm going to click
我的文本工具，然后我要点击
on the canvas and I'm going to use the
在画布上，我将使用
letters c and b for this demonstration I
本演示中的字母c和b为i
found that these letters work really
我发现这些字母真的很管用
well together but this works with pretty
在一起很好，但这对漂亮的
much any letter as long as you're using
任何字母，只要你在使用
this font and I'm going to select the
此字体和我要选择的
letters and I'll open up my text editor
字母，我会打开我的文本编辑器
by going to text and going to text and
通过转到文本和转到文本和
font and the font I'm looking for is
字体，我要找的字体是
called winner so I'm going to type that
名为Winner，所以我要输入
in and apply it and now we have the font
然后应用它，现在我们就有了字体
applied so let me collapse this menu I'm
申请了，所以让我把这份菜单折叠一下
going to grab my selection tool and I'm
去拿我的选择工具，然后我
going to in increase the size of this
将增加这一项目的规模
I'm going to hold my control key while I
我要按住我的控制键
do that so we can scale it up
这样我们就可以扩大规模了
proportionately and I'm going to place
在比例上，我要把
it in the center of the page so now
它在页面的中心，所以现在
let's convert this from a text object to
让我们将其从文本对象转换为
a path by going to path and selecting
通过转到Path并选择
object to path and then we want to split
对象到路径，然后我们想要拆分
the letters apart so I'll go back to the
字母分开了，所以我要回到
path menu and I will choose split path
路径菜单，我将选择拆分路径
and now we have two separate letters and
现在我们有两封不同的信
I'll zoom in on this so you can see it
我会把这个放大，这样你就能看到它了
better so what we're going to do here is
更好的是，我们现在要做的是
I'm going to take this letter C and I'm
我要用这个字母C，我是
going to collapse its height and then
它的高度会坍塌，然后
elongate it so that it can intertwine
把它拉长，这样它就可以缠绕在一起了
with this letter B here here and to do
带着这个字母B在这里和做
that we're going to use the nodes tool
我们将使用节点工具
so let me select the letter and then
所以让我选择字母，然后
I'll come over to my nodes tool and I'm
我会来到我的节点工具前，然后我
going to click and drag over these nodes
在这些节点上单击并拖动
to select them and then I'm going to
来选择它们，然后我要
click and drag them down I'm going to
点击并将它们拖到下面，我要
hold my control key while I do that and
在我这样做的时候按住我的控制键，然后
click and drag to bring these nodes down
单击并拖动以按下这些节点
like this we want this letter C to fit
像这样，我们想让这个字母C适合
within this letter B uh and in order to
在这封信中，呃，为了
do that we need to shrink that down now
真的吗？我们现在需要把它缩小
a problem I'm running into here is that
我在这里遇到的一个问题是
this part of the design this part of the
这一部分的设计这部分
letter anyway is starting to collapse in
不管怎么说，这封信开始崩溃了
on itself so I'm going to move these up
所以我要把这些往上移
a little bit I'm going to select just
有一点我要选择
these nodes right here and I'm going to
这些节点就在这里，我要
use my arrow keys to move them up I'm
使用我的箭头键向上移动它们，我是
going to use my up Arrow key and I'm
使用我的向上箭头键，我将
going to count the number of steps that
我来数一数每一步
I used to move these nodes because I
我过去常常移动这些节点，因为我
want to move these nodes over here down
想要将这些节点向下移动到这里
by the same number of steps so I'm going
以相同的步数，所以我要
to press the up Arrow key 1 2 3 four
按向上箭头键1 2 3 4
five six seven
5 6 7
eight 15 times and I'll do the same
8次15次，我也会这么做
thing down here I'm going to select
下面是我要选择的东西
these nodes and I'll move them down 15
这些节点，我会将它们下移15
Steps as well 1 2 3
步数也是1 2 3
4 and we do that just to maintain the
4我们这样做只是为了维护
symmetry tree so let me grab my
对称树，所以让我拿起我的
selection tool now and I'm going to move
现在选择工具，我要移动
this letter over here and put it on top
把这封信放在上面
of the letter B where I would like it to
字母B在我想要的位置
be and I'll go back to my nodes tool and
BE和我将返回到我的节点工具并
I'm just going to use the nodes tool to
我只是要使用节点工具来
select these nodes and adjust the size
选择这些节点并调整大小
of this some more so I'm going to hold
更多的，所以我要拿着
control while I do this so it locks it
控件，同时执行此操作，以便它锁定它
onto the horizontal axis while I move
在我移动的时候放到水平轴上
these nodes and I'm going to collapse
这些节点和我将要崩溃
this down a little more what I'm paying
这比我付的要低一点
attention to right here is where the arm
注意这里就是手臂的位置
of the C intersects with the um negative
C与这个负数相交
space of the letter B here I want the
字母B的空格在这里我想要
this to be roughly halfway through so
这大概是一半的时间
let me move this up a little bit and now
让我把这个往上移一点，现在
it looks like it's going about halfway
看起来好像已经走了一半了
through and I'll do the same thing to
我也会做同样的事
these top nodes over here I'll move
我要把这些顶部的节点移到这里
these ones down and again I'm holding
这些都放下了，我又一次握住了
control the whole time I do this to make
控制我做这件事的整个时间
sure that we're locking it onto the
我们肯定会把它锁在
vertical
垂向
axis and what I'll do now is I'll grab
轴心，我现在要做的是
my selection tool and I will select both
我的选择工具和我将选择两者
of these letters and I'm going to open
这些信件，我要打开
up my alignment menu by going over to
通过转到我的对准菜单
object and selecting aligned distribute
对象并选择对齐分布
and I want to choose last selected and
我想选择上一次选中的和
I'm just going to make sure that they
我只是要确保他们
are aligned horizontally and vertically
水平和垂直对齐
and then I'll collapse this menu and
然后我会把这个菜单折叠起来
what we can do now is I'm going to make
我们现在能做的是我要做的是
a duplicate copy of these two letters so
这两封信的复印件
I'm going to rightclick them and go to
我要右键单击它们并转到
duplicate and I want to make offset
复制，我想进行补偿
copies of these so with them selected
这些SO的副本，并选择它们
I'm going to go to path and I'm going to
我要去PATH，我要去
select outset and that's going to
选择开始，这将是
increase the offset of the letters and
增加字母和字母的偏移量
I'm going to do that a couple of more
我还会再做几次
times uh this offset represents the
乘以呃这个偏移量表示
spacing that's going to be between the
它的间距将介于
letters when they're overlapping each
当字母相互重叠时
other so depending on how large or small
其他视大小而定
is you may want to repeat this step a
您可能想要重复此步骤a
few more times I'm going to repeat this
我要再重复几次
one more time I'm going to choose
我要再选一次
outset and maybe I'll do it one more
一开始，也许我会再来一次
time just because I have my letters
时间只因为我有我的信
pretty large I'll go to path outset and
很大，我将去路径开始和
now that's looking much bigger than the
现在这看起来比
original letters so what we want to do
原创信件所以我们想要做的是
now is let's click and drag over
现在让我们点击并拖动到
everything we want to select everything
一切我们想要选择的一切
and now we can use the shape Builder
现在我们可以使用Shape Builder
tool to morph this into what we want it
工具，把它变成我们想要的东西
to be so I'm going to come over here to
就这样，我要来这里
the shape Builder tool and I'm going to
Shape Builder工具和我将
zoom in on this and I want to make sure
放大这个，我想确保
I have the plus icon selected here the
我在这里选择了加号图标
add option and now I can just click and
添加选项，现在我只需点击并
drag through the areas of the design and
在设计区域中拖动，然后
shape it how I would like it to be
把它塑造成我想要的样子
shaped so I'm going to click and drag
所以我要点击并拖动
through this part of the design right
通过这一部分的设计权
here because I want this part of the
这是因为我想要这一部分
letter B to overlap this part of the
字母B与此部分重叠
letter c and then I want this part of
字母c，然后我想要这部分
the letter c to overlap the letter B
字母c与字母B重叠
over here and then we get that effect so
在这里，然后我们会得到这样的效果
I'll come down here and repeat this but
我会下来重复这句话，但是
the opposite way I'm going to make this
相反，我要用相反的方式做这个
part overlap and then I'll make this
部分重叠，然后我会做这个
part overlap and then I'm going to click
部分重叠，然后我将单击
on this part right here to highlight it
在这部分上突出显示它
in blue now it's important that you
现在穿着蓝色的衣服很重要
highlight everything that you want to
突出显示您想要的所有内容
keep in blue you have to click on it to
保持蓝色，你必须点击它才能
highlight it in blue and if you don't do
用蓝色突出显示它，如果您不这样做
that it's going to be deleted once
它将被删除一次
you're finished so everything that's
你完蛋了，所以一切都结束了
gray is going to be deleted everything
格雷将被删除所有内容
that's not blue is going to be deleted
不是蓝色的将被删除
and once you're finished you can press
一旦你完成了，你就可以按
the check mark button up here and just
复选标记按钮就在这里
like that we have created an
就这样，我们创建了一个
interlocking letter logo using the shape
联锁字母标志使用的形状
Builder tool in inkscape if you found
Inkscape中的构建器工具，如果您找到
this lesson useful then consider
这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这段视频中所做的
even have a private Community where you
甚至拥有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
can ask questions and get help from me
可以问我问题并得到我的帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何你想要的时间，最好的是有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
你只需支付月费就可以了
$17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次17美元，你就会被判终身监禁
have some information about that down
我有一些关于这方面的信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想要将其查看为
always thanks for
永远感谢你
watching
观看
oh
噢